with you
hands oh don't you recognize me you may
call yourself my brother but you are not
the Genji on you
so this is the one hand become of ear a
pity they will not be judged by you
it is not too late to change a course
brother you are mistaken brother I am
beyond redemption
together we could have built an empire
server your dream no mine you will never
amount to editing we shall see brother
what would our father think of what
we've become brother it's hard to say
who he'd been more disappointed by
think you can do better than me I am
certain of it
today brother those were yo amusements
not mine
you might be fast Genji but you ain't
faster than a bullet why don't we find
out
you seem very dandy I am a different man
now I am whole
I got you some chocolates kenji Swiss
they're the best trade you Angela
perhaps you could share them with me
Angela I have some chocolates for you
not Swiss huh I suppose it will have to
do Thank You candy
kenji this is just like old times our
paths cross for now as to the future we
shall see
I always liked working with you Winston
no awkward small talk always liked
working with you too
you have great sense of humor
how do I trust a man who is half machine
the heart of a man still beats inside
it is good to fight alongside one of my
brightest pupils and you matter
suffering of the AMEX here traveling
master it does my brother Mon Dada did
much to improve their lives but it was
not to be
you wouldn't believe what I learned
about you Sparrow I am at peace with who
I was your threat does not concern me
I am victorious this time brother
at your own peril
I have the upper hand this time matter
Minju brother
sir
Angela